Linda LaMacchia collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1: Fieldwork in Northwest India
  - Subseries 1: Dissertation fieldwork
    - Interviews
      - [Hindi interview with Sushmila in Spello], July 2-4, 1996, afc2017049_dc09; 1 text file (wpd)
      - Hirapal Ganga Negi, April 2, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/39)
      - Hirmal interview, October 9, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, afc2017049_dc09; 2 text files (wpd, doc)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR045; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Jangsem in Sapni, August 18, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 1/40)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR048, SR049, SR050, SR066; 4 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - January 5, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR136; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Jita Sen Negi interview], January 18, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/4)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR121; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Jomo interviews], December 1991
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR016; 1 sound cassette
      - July 1, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR090; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - July 14, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR052; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - July 15, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR053; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - June 6, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR057; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Khempo Thupten in Sarnath, Wangchu Dorje translator, 1996, afc2017049_dc50; 3 audio files (mp3)
      - Khenpo Thupten Woser (Pangaon abbot) tape, February 10, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/2)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR071, SR084; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Konchok Gyaltsen interview], January 8, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/5)
      - Konchok Gyaltsen on Drikung Khandro 1A, January 8, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/3)
      - Lochen Tulku, April 2, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/4)
      - [Lotsa Rinpoche interview], April 2, 1996, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (doc)
      - March 11, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR061; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - May 21-22, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR095; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Namgyal, Geden Choeling, April 28, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR002, SR142; 1 sound cassette; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Nelchorma 1A, B, Dharmsala, April 21, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/5)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (doc)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR140, SR142 (Side A); 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - October 1, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR109; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Ramesh Chandra interview, January 21, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR042; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Sempa Dorjo (Po) Sarnath, March 24, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/6)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (doc)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR084, SR063; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - September 13, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR103; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - September 14, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR106; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - September 21, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR105, SR110; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - September 22, 1995, AFC 2017/049: SR107, SR108; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - September 7, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR044; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - September 27, 1996, AFC 2017/049: SR047; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Sonam Dekyi tape 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B, December 12, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/7)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/6)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR128, SR123; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Tenzin Choeden, May 10, 1992, AFC 2017/049: SR011; 1 sound cassette
      - [Tenzin Choeden interview], October 18, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/7)
      - Tenzin Choeden & Tsultrim Angmo (Pangaon) (see also back of Chos Nyid Zangmo) - 2A, 2B, 1B, October 18-19, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Tenzin Dedin, Jamyang Choeling, June 5-6, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR096, SR098; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Tenzin Dolma (Pangaon) tape 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B, 3A; 3B, 1B, October 15-19, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/11)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/8)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR111, SR112, SR114, SR113; 4 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Tenzin Kinzum 2A, 1B, 2A, 2B, 3A, December 15-19, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/12)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR126, SR129, SR127, SR130; 4 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Tenzin Nangsal & Thupten Choezing (of Kanam in Dharamsala), September 30-November 18, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/13)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/9)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR120, SR122; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Tenzin Tsomo interview], January 25, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/10)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR041; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Tenzin Zangmo (Jamyang Choeling of Kanam) tape 1A, 1B, 2A, 2B (Yongchen Dolma attached page 1), December 21, 1995
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/14)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/11)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR130, SR133; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Thupten Woser interview], February 10, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Tibetan [translation notebook], November 15, 1994, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Transcribing Tz Dedin, Hirapal Ganga Negi [notebook], 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Transcriptions [notebook], 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/17)
      - [Translation and transcription notebook], 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/18)
      - [Tsultrim Angmo interview], October 19, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/13)
      - Upal Devi (Kanam) at Toso, translated Hirapel Negi, 1A, Siam and Bodhi (Lobsang Tsultrim) three teachers, journey to Tibet, July 2, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/19)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR067; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Vidhya Sagar Negi, Jita Sen Negi, Ramesh Chandra, Sempa Dorje (Sarnath, letter, notes, tapes) 1A, 1B, quote Buddhist Records of the Western World, February 29, 1996
        - Interview transcripts; field notes, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/20)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR139, SR138; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Vidhya Sagar Negi interview], February 29, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/14)
      - Wangju Dorje (notes) (tape 1B, 1A/B), January 26-March 22, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/21)
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/15)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc08; 1 text file (doc)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR138, SR060; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Yongchen Dolma (of Nichar in Sarnath), Tenzen Tsomo (of Kanam in Sarnath), Lippa astrologer, 1A, 1B, 1A (notes), January 25-27, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/22)
      - [Yongchen Dolma interview], January 25, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/16)
      - Yulgyal Tulku tape 1B, 2A (translated Wangchuk Dorje), July 6, 1996
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 2/23)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR064, SR055; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
    - Field note journals
      - Hirmal, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Jangi and Moorang, Jangi to Rerang, September 9-22, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/2)
      - [Journal entries], April-July 1996, afc2017049_dc08; Chandra Mani, Chosem Dolma of Bari, Hirapal Ganga Negi, Lochen Tulku, Panang (Gautam Nagar), Ribba, Spello, Tabo.; 8 text files (wpd)
      - [Journal entries], July 1996, afc2017049_dc07; Sonam Deva (in Khadura) on Chatan Mani, Hirmal.; 2 text files (wpd)
      - [Journal entries], August-September 1996, afc2017049_dc09; Jangi, Lippa, Moorang, Rnam Thar of Negi Rinpoche, Nichar, Ribba, Sapni.; 7 text files (wpd)
      - Lippa - third trip to Kinnaur (Journal #3), September 10, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Nichar - Bari - (third trip to Kinnaur), September 2, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Notebook #1: Air France to Dharamsala, August 13-October 3, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/5)
      - Notebook #2: McLeod Ganj to Panwi/Wangtha (Gautam Nagar), October 3-December 2, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Notebook #3: Jangi to Sarnath, December 2, 1995-January 25, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Notebook #4: Sarnath to Dharamsala, January 24-May 3, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Notebook #5: Telokpur to Nichar, May 4-July 19, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Notebook #6: Nichar to Sapni, July 19-August 17, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Notebook #7: Sapni to Ribba, August 18-27, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/1)
      - Notebook #8: Ribba to Rarang, August 27-September 15, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/2)
      - Notebook #9: Rarang to Bari, September 16-October 12, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/3)
      - Notebook #10: Simla to Delhi (to 3/14/97 Madison), October 16, 1996-March 14, 1997, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/4)
      - Notebook #11: Transcriptions of tapes, 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/5)
      - Panang (Panwi) - also Jangi, Gautam Nagar, Yulgyal Tulku and family, November 27, 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/6)
      - Ribba - Kanam - Chango, June 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/7)
      - Ribba - Journal 3 (disc), August 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/8)
      - Sapni - Tl 3 (disc), August 18, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/9)
      - Spello - Jangi - Samarka - Tokto - Lippa - Rarang - Nichar, Notebook #5, July 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/10)
      - Tabo, Kalachorra, June 22-July 3, 1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Graphic materials
      - India jomos, lamas, and puppy, 1990-2013, afc2017049_dc52; 92 still image files (jpg)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1990, AFC 2017/049: PH017; 37 color slides (35 mm) (Box 11)
      - Delhi, Dharamsala, nuns Ladnun, Acharya Tulsi (Jaipur), February-March 1991, AFC 2017/049: PH002; 33 color slides (35 mm) (Box 8)
      - Manali (Sola Mil), May-June 1991, AFC 2017/049: PH003; 20 color slides (35 mm) (Box 8)
      - Shungsep, September 4-15, 1995, 25 black-and-white negatives (35 mm); 2 black-and-white contact sheets; AFC 2017/049: PH037 (Box 15, Box 12)
      - Shungsep, Jamyang Choeling, Linda in Kinnauri "Daru," September 15-23, 1995, 24 black-and-white negatives (35 mm); 2 black-and-white contact sheets; AFC 2017/049: PH024 (Box 12, Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], September-October 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH004; 24 color slides (35 mm) (Box 8)
      - Dosa, Kinnaur, October-November 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH006; 20 color slides (35 mm) (Box 9)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH038; 28 black-and-white prints (4x6) (Box 14)
      - Daru, circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH034; 8 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH031; 28 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH032; 18 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH033; 25 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH036; 37 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1995, AFC 2017/049: PH048; 4 black-and-white prints (4x6); 3 color prints (4x6) (Box 15)
      - Photos (1996 and earlier, lama and jomos, puppy), circa 1995-1996, AFC 2017/049: PH042; 17 color prints (4x6); 8 black-and-white prints (4x6) (Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], June-November 1996, AFC 2017/049: PH005; 109 color slides (35 mm) (Box 9)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 1996, AFC 2017/049: PH035; 3 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 1996, 40 color negatives (35 mm); 20 black-and-white prints (4x6); AFC 2017/049: PH021 (Box 13, Box 14)
      - Spello jomo photo, undated, afc2017049_dc16; 1 still image file (jpg)
    - Administrative files
      - A Kinnauri Nun's Song, 1993, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/12)
      - [Correspondence about fieldwork], 1992-1995, afc2017049_dc05; 3 text files (wpd, eps)
      - [Correspondence about fieldwork], 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/13)
      - [Correspondence about fieldwork], 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 7/17)
      - Gerard, Kinnauri languages, undated, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/14)
      - Nam Thar of Shungsep Jetsun translated by T. Allione, 1994, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/15)
      - [Nam Thar of Shungsep Jetsun Lochen Rinpoche translation] September 29, 1994, AFC 2017/049: SR010; 1 sound cassette
      - [Partial grant application], 1997, afc2017049_dc07; 1 text file (wpd)
      - "Questionnaire" for nuns interviews (guidelines), circa 1995, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/16)
      - [Recording logs], 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/17)
      - Sound studio tapes, 1995-1996, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/18)
  - Subseries 2: Additional fieldwork
    Interviews, songs, field note journals, photographs, and video footage collected during LaMacchia's subsequent trips to the Kinnaur district of Northwest India. See Appendix B for a list of interview subjects.
    - Songs
      - Ar Meera, Kinnauri songs; Ar Kenaur, Loser songs, 2008-2009, afc2017049_dc49; 4 audio files (mp3)
      - Bag Chand Kinnauri, August 2014, AFC 2017/049: SR037; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Jangi lama-jomos Bag Chand, August 16, 2014, AFC 2017/049: SR040; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Kinnauri songs (Ropa) audio part 1, January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc28; Track list: 1, Song of Nyima Zangmo (Ropa version); 2, Song of Guru Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 3, Song of Ropa Tholpa; 4, Song of Guru Rinpoche (part 2 of 2); 5, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Ropa version); 6, Song of Jetsun Mila.; 6 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri songs (Ropa) part 1, January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc40; Track list: 1, Song of Nyima Zangmo (Ropa version); 2, Song of Guru Rinpoche (part 1 of 2); 3, Song of Ropa Tholpa; 4, Song of Guru Rinpoche (part 2 of 2); 5, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Ropa version); 6, Song of Jetsun Mila; 6 audio files (mp3), 1 text file (xml)
      - Kinnauri songs Ropa, January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc38; Track list: 1, Song of Nyima Zangmo (Ropa version); 2, Song of Guru Rinpoche (Padmasambhava); 3, Song of Guru Rinpoche, sequel, verses 29-45; 4, Song of Lotsa Rinpoche (Ropa version); 5, Song of Negi lama (Ropa version); 6, Song of Lippa lama (Sonam Dupke); 7, Song of Jetsun Mila (Milarepa's statue) of Ropa.; 7 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc28, afc2017049_dc38, and afc2017049_dc40, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/3)
      - Kinnauri songs (Ropa and Sunnam) audio part 2, December 28, 2002-January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc29; 4 audio files (wav)
      - Kinnauri songs (Ropa and Sunnam) part 2, December 28, 2002-January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc41; Track list: 1, Song of Nyima Zangmo (Sunnam version); 2, Song of Buddha Shakyamuni (Ropa version); 3, Song of Negi Lama (Ropa version); 4, Song of Sonam Dupke (Lippa lama).; 4 audio files (mp3), 1 text file (xml)
      - Kinnauri songs Ropa and Sunnam, December 28, 2002-January 5, 2003, afc2017049_dc39; 3 audio files (wav)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc29, afc2017049_dc39, and afc2017049_dc41, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/6)
      - Lobsang Buddha githang, August 19, 2014, AFC 2017/049: SR031; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Losar songs Kanum; songs of Ropa, 2002-2003, 2009
        - Song transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/19)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR078, SR080, SR077, SR081, SR083; 5 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Song translations], 2002-2003, 1 folder (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Interviews
      - [Interview with Choegon Rinpoche], November 18, 2008, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/1)
      - [Interview with Choegon Rinpoche], January 2013, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/2)
      - [Interview with jomo Dr. Tenzin Yangkyi], October 29, 2008
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/3)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR076 (Side B); 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Ponlop Rinpoche], May 11, 2012
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/4)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR087; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Professor Wangchuk Dorje], May 2, 2015
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/5)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR039; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Tenzin Palyon (Shanti)], September 24, 2008
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/6)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR085 (Side A); 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Ven. Shanti], April 2, 2015
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/7)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR036; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Ven. Sonam Dekyi], April 26, 2015
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/8)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR032; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Interview with Ven. Thupten Choezing], June 14, 2015
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/9)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR038; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Interviews [Menri, Ponlop, Sonam Choeden], 2012
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/10)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR073, SR094; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - [Interviews with Ven. Tenzin Zangmo and Lobsang Dolma], 2008, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/11)
      - Side A: J.C. Tz Zangmo; Side B: Dehra Dun Choegen R., November 15-18, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR072; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Kachen Lama interview in Shumcho Kanum, 2003, afc2017049_dc02; 2 audio files (mp3)
      - [Khenchen Konchok Gyaltsen], June 10, 2006
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/12)
        - Sound recordings, AFC 2017/049: SR091, SR034; 2 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Side A: Lippa, Kanam; Side B: Kanam nuns in Dharmsala, December 19, 2009-January 7, 2010, AFC 2017/049: SR070; 1 sound cassettes (microcassette)
      - Side A: Lippa Lobsang, Lobsang John; Side B: Hirmal, October 10-14, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR069; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - March 13, 2015, AFC 2017/049: SR035; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Negi Lama Rnam Thar, May 5, 2005, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/13)
      - New Years transcripts and translations, December 2009-February 2010
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/14)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR075; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Side A: Nichar; Side B: Meeru, October 30-November 1, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR086; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Side A: Noise and Bob; Side B: Noise and John, March 19-20, 2015, AFC 2017/049: SR068; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - [Ontul Rinpoche on Drikung Khandro], June 29, 1998
        - Interview transcripts, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/15)
        - Interview transcript, afc2017049_dc09; 1 text file (wpd)
        - Sound recording, AFC 2017/049: SR088; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Puja Meeru, 21 Tarias, November 1, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR079; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - RCN, April 27, 2012, AFC 2017/049: SR092; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Side A: Spello Yandrol, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR076; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Tenzin's sister, Kanam Kusum, 2013, AFC 2017/049: SR074; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
      - Side A: Tz Deden; Side B: Lobsang Rohra, September 29-October 10, 2008, AFC 2017/049: SR082; 1 sound cassette (microcassette)
    - Field note journals
      - [Journal notes on Drikung Khandro], 2005-2006, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/16)
      - Research diary - Gyalber Negi, Ropa Jomo, 2002-2003, 1 folder (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Graphic materials
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 2002-2003, AFC 2017/049: PH007; 36 color slides (35 mm) (Box 9)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 2002-2003, AFC 2017/049: PH041; 7 color prints (4x6); Some of the prints have labels on the back identifying photo subject. (Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2003, AFC 2017/049: PH022; 40 color negatives (35 mm); Prints have labels on the back identifying photo subject. (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2007, AFC 2017/049: PH018; 25 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2007, AFC 2017/049: PH019; 25 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2007, AFC 2017/049: PH020; 22 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2007, AFC 2017/049: PH023; 8 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2007, AFC 2017/049: PH028; 40 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 2008, AFC 2017/049: PH008; 44 color slides (35 mm) (Box 9)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], 2008, AFC 2017/049: PH008; 20 color slides (35 mm) (Box 10)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2008-circa 2012, AFC 2017/049: PH043; 1 black-and-white contact sheet; 2 color contact sheets; 28 color prints (4x6); 1 black-and-white print (4x6) (Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2011, 24 color negatives (35 mm); 5 color contact sheets; AFC 2017/049: PH029 (Box 13, Box 14)
      - Puppy's ashes, New Years dance, dogs, cow, Dolanyi, Meeru Lobseng, Sarabai, Spello, Sarorka, September 2012, afc2017049_dc55; 33 still images (jpg), 1 text file (xml)
      - Manuscript material accompanying digital media: afc2017049_dc55, 1 folder (Box-folder 16/7)
      - India trip, December 2012-February 2013, afc2017049_dc01; 48 still image files (jpg)
      - India trip and 70th birthday, August-October 2013, afc2017049_dc56; 72 still images (jpg)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2013, 28 color negatives (35 mm); 12 color prints (4x6); AFC 2017/049: PH026 (Box 13, Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2013, AFC 2017/049: PH027; 37 black-and-white negatives (35 mm) (Box 12)
      - India, circa 2013, AFC 2017/049: PH040; 3 color contact sheets (Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2013, AFC 2017/049: PH044; 6 color prints (4x6) (Box 14)
      - [Fieldwork in Northwest India], circa 2013, AFC 2017/049: PH045; 4 color prints (4x6) (Box 14)
      - India trip, July-September 2014, AFC 2017/049: PH030; 40 color negatives (35 mm) (Box 13)
      - India trip, July-September 2014, afc2017049_dc54; 72 still images (jpg)